■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
翻译  麦克姜 不高兴童鞋 胖兔纯
翻译  瑒瑒 兮之 roaddog
校对  roaddog 不高兴童鞋
时间轴 想念Gallifrey的wholock 贝贝
后期  吉吉  总监 roaddog
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
球手
第一季  第一集
*在天空翱翔*
*Take a ride in the sky*
*乘坐幻想飞船*
*On our ship fantasize*
*一切梦想瞬间成真*
*All your dreams will come true right away*
宝贝
Baby.
我爱你
I love you.
是吗  我也爱你
Hell, yeah, you do. Love you, too, girl.
-真的吗  -当然
- Do you really? - Yeah.
-认真的吗  -你怎么老问我这个
- I mean, are you sure? - Why you always ask me that?
我爱你  不管你问多少遍
You ask me that a lot. I do.
有多爱
How much?
这种事情怎么能量化呢
Got to quantify every damn thing, huh, baby?
我只是想听你说出来
Maybe I just like to hear you say it.
-那我就再说一遍  -好
- Maybe I'll just say it again. - Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
过来
Bring it in here.
胜过世间一切
More than anything, baby.
胜过橄榄球吗
More than football?
当然胜过橄榄球
More than ball. Come on, now.
那和年度最佳新秀奖杯比呢
More than your Rookie of the Year trophy?
-奖杯算个屁  -好吧
- Fuck that trophy. - All right.
超级碗冠军戒指呢
How about that Super Bowl ring?
这就是个装饰而已
It's just jewelry, baby.
所以你愿意为我做任何事吗
So you would do anything for me?
因为你知道我愿意为你做任何事
'Cause, baby, you know I'd do anything for you.
哪怕是舍弃我的性命
Even kill myself.
没错  任何事  宝贝
Yup, absolutely anything, baby.
包括离开你妻子吗
Even leave your wife?
-你这个骗子  我就知道  -冷静点
- You motherfucker. I knew it. - Hey, relax.
你跟我说你们分居了
You told me you were separated.
别抱怨这么多  根本没必要
Well, stop labeling every damn thing because you don't have to.
你这个骗子  我调查过了
You lying piece of shit. I checked.